Guide to the Family planning, birth control, and sexuality publications,circa 1934-2004.
Family planning, birth control, and sexuality publications,circa 1934-1989, 2000.
- Series III. Publications and Subject Files
  - Population Bulletin: Hawaii: Growing Pains in Paradise, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Population Bulletin: Suburban Growth--A Case Study, February 1972 (Box 2)
  - Population Bulletin: Fertility Regulation Technology: Status and Prospects, March 1977 (Box 2)
  - Population Bulletin: Boys or Girls? Parents' Preferences and Sex Control, January 1978 (Box 2)
  - Population Bulletin: What Will A ZPG Society Be Like?, January 1978 (Box 2)
  - Population Bulletin: The 1980 Census: The Countering of America, September 1979 (Box 2)
  - Population Bulletin: America's Baby Boom Generation; The Fateful Bulge, April 1980 (Box 2)
- Series IV. Educational Aids
  - Population Facts at Hand (United Nations Fund for Population Activities [UNFPA]), 1980 (Box 2)
  - "Scientific American: Population Issue", September 1974 (Box 2)
  - "Social Education: Population Issue", April 1972 (Box 2)
  - "Expanding Roles: Opportunities for Youth Leadership in Overcoming Sex-Role Stereotypes" (Developed by Community Service Education Department NYS College of Human Ecology) (Box 3)
  - The People Pack: Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc. (fact cards) (Box 2)
Separated Material
Sex and You. By Roz Kenworthy with Hope Perry and Dina Seidman. Cornell University. July 1978.
Sex: A Fact Book. 1977-78. By Roz Kenworthy with Hope Perry, Andrew Larkin, Sharon DiGeronimo, Planned Parenthood staff, and Barbara Tarbell. Cornell University. July 1977.
Sex: A Fact Book (How Not To Blow It). By Roz Kenworthy with Steven A. Wartman. Cornell University. July 1975.
Sex Information. By Roz Kenworthy with Elizabeth S. McLellan and Steven A. Wartman. Cornell University. July 1974.
Sex Information for Cornell Students. By Rosalind Kenworthy with Susan Annis, Jessica Bram, and Elizabeth S. McLellan. Cornell University. August 1972.
Sex: Beyond the Birds and the Bees. By Katherine Comeau, Larry Etzweiler, Abby Ginzberg, Rosalind Kenworthy, Elizabeth McLellan, Kristi Rohlf, and Debbie Ross. Cornell University. August 1971.
No title. First sex handbook by the Dean of Students Office. Cornell University. 1970.
The AIDS Crisis in New York: A Legislative Perspective and Agenda for Study. Prepared by the Staff of the New York State Senate Majority Task Force on AIDS. June 1987.
Pregnant Too Soon: Adoption is an Option. By Jeanne Warren Lindsay. Morning Glory Press. 1980.
The Time Has Come: A Catholic Doctor's Proposals to End the Battle over Birth Control. By John Rock. Alfred A. Knopf. 1963.
Growth Patterns and Sex Education. Prepared by the Committee on Health Guidance in Sex Education. American School Health Association. 1978.
Adolescent Sexuality in a Changing American Society: Social and Psychological Perspectives. By Catherine S. Chilman. U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare. Circa 1977.
Growing Up with Sex. By Richard F. Hettlinger. The Seabury Press. 1971.
What to Tell Your Child About Sex. Prepared by The Child Study Association of America. Pocket Book. 1974.
What Shall I Tell My Child? Crown Publishers. 1970.
The Stork is Dead. By Charlie W. Shedd. Pillar Books. 1976.
What Your Child Really Wants to Know About Sex and Why. By Dr. William A. Block. Fawcett Publications. October 1974.
Sex Before 20: New Answers for Youth. By Helen F. Southard. The New American Library. August 1968.
Population. By Roland Pressat. Penguin Books. 1971.
Population Control. Edited by Anthony Allison. Penguin Books. 1970.
Famine - 1975!: America's Decision: Who Will Survive? By William and Paul Paddock. Little, Brown and Company. 1967.
The Problem of Population II:Practical Catholic Applications. University of Notre Dame Press. December 1964.
Breeding Ourselves to Death. By Lawrence Lader. Ballantine Books. 1971.
The Rhythm Way to Family Happiness. By John P. Murphy and John D. Laux. Hawthorn Books. 1968.
The Natural Way to Family Planning. By John P. Murphy and John D. Laux. Practical Publishers. 1980.
The Pill: Facts and Fallacies About Today's Oral Contraceptives. By Robert W. Kistner. Delacorte Pres. 1969.
The Hungary Planet: The Modern World at the Edge of Famine. By Georg Borgstrom. Collier Books. 1972.
Sexuality in Society. By John W. Petras. Allyn and Bacon. 1973.
People!: Challenge to Survival. By William Vogt. William Sloane Associates. 1960.
Population: The Vital Revolution. Edited by Ronald Freedman. Anchor Books. 1964.
An Analysis of Human Sexual Response. Edited by Ruth and Edward Brecher. The New American Library. 1966.
After You're Out. Edited by Karla Jay and Allen Young. Pyramid Books. 1975.
A Doctor Speaks on Sexual Expression in Marriage. By Donald W. Hastings. Bantam Books. 1966.
The New You. By Sol Gordon. Bantam Books. 1979.
Your Body: A Reference Book for Women. By Jack M. Futoran and May Annexton. Ballantine Books. 1976.
Love and Sex in Plain Language. By Eric W. Johnson. Bantam Books. 1970.
Why Males Exist: An Inquiry into the Evolution of Sex. ByFred Hapgood. The New American Library. 1979.
Sexuality and Man. Prepared by Sex Information and Education Council of the U.S. Charles Scribner's Sons. 1970.
The Advocate Guide to Gay Health. By R.D. Fenwick. Alyson Publications. November 1982.
The Church and Sex. By R. F. Trevett. Hawthorn Books. 1960.
Islam and Family Planning. By Ahmad El-Sharabassy, translated by Sayed Ismail A. R. Egyptian Family Planning Association. 1969.
The Female Eunuch. By Germaine Greer. McGraw-Hill Book Co. 1971.
Contraceptive Technology 1976-1977 8th Revised Edition. By Robert A. Hatcher et al. Irvington Publishers. 1976.
Contraceptive Technology 1978-1979 9th Revised Edition. By Robert A. Hatcher et al. Irvington Publishers. 1978.
Contraceptive Technology 1980-1981 10th Revised Edition. By Robert A. Hatcher et al. Irvington Publishers. 1980.
Contraceptive Technology 1982-1983 11th Revised Edition. By Robert A. Hatcher et al. Irvington Publishers. 1982.
Contraceptive Technology 1984-1985 12th Revised Edition. By Robert A. Hatcher et al. Irvington Publishers. 1984.
Contraceptive Technology 1986-1987 13th Revised Edition. By Robert A. Hatcher et al. Irvington Publishers. 1986.
Sex & Society in Sweden. By Birgitta Linner. Random House. 1967.
Birth Control: Its Use and Misuse. By Dorothy Dunbar Bromley. Harper & Brothers Publishers. 1934.
Gay: What You Should Know About Homosexuality. By Morton Hunt. Pocket Books. 1977.
The Ethics of Sexual Acts. By Rene Guyon. Blue Ribbon Books. 1941.
The Vaginal Diaphragm: Its Fitting and Use in Contraceptive Technique. By Le Mon Clark. The C. V. Mosby Co. 1939.